I knew the man was crazy,
but not that crazy!
Straightzo!
I'm going to give you a choice on
how you want to meet your demise.
Will it be plain old sunlight or Hamon?
Or I could just smash in your brains!
How would you feel about that?
He's going to kill us all!
Huh?
Jojo, would you lose your mind?
Just look at what you've done!
Yeah, I know.
It'll take a small fortune to
fix everything in this place.
Not that!
You just shot a person!
Person?
You mean straighter?
These bullets I fired at him
all have strange dents in them.
They've been completely warped.
Smokey, get out of here, now.
That thing I shot, I can only
hope that he was a person.
And if he was, I'll happily go to jail
without thinking twice about it. What?
I don't...
What else would he be?
Can we please stop the crying?
I'm trying to think here.
If you don't calm down, I may
have to make out with you.
I don't know.
Thank
you.
Thank you.
Dio's failure was in his
infatuation with his own power.
He just couldn't resist
constantly pushing his own limits.
He stretched himself thin,
allowing Jonathan to strike him.
But I have a different philosophy.
I figure I'll have plenty
of time to reflect on
the extent of my powers
after you're destroyed.
There will be no mercy for you.
I thought it would be
appropriate to open up
with the technique that
Dio used to kill Jonathan.
Guns will fail.
However, I can fire high-pressure
essence from my eyes.
Look deeply into my space-ripper's
stingy eyes, Joseph!
JoJo!
That was a little too easy.
Now, the only one left is Arena Joestar.
And that should be...
I know what you'll say next.
About as easy as taking candy from a baby.
Hmm.
Next thing you'll say is...
How could he possibly be alive
with that hole in his head?
Am I right?
But how could he possibly be
alive with that hole in his head?
Too much time meditating out in the
Tibetan boonies has dulled your senses.
That's why I like this city.
It keeps you sharp.
You wouldn't be so confused right now if
you had just been a bit more observant.
All right, here's a hint.
You wouldn't happen to
have the time, would you?
I heard the story about Dio
taking down my grandfather.
by firing some sort of blast
from his eyes. A mirror!
Look who finally noticed!
Straight, Zof!
I also heard that you
may be severely allergic
to Hamon just as much
as you are to sunlight!
Batter up!
Here comes the pinch!
Let's out of here! Yeah!
So, I hear that Hamon does a pretty
good job of melting vampire faces.
Let's have a look here.
He's unharmed!
It's as though I never
even touched him at all.
Could it be possible
that Granny was wrong?
Not at all.
Your Granny was not wrong,
because I can see that
you would grow into quite
a worthy foe if I didn't
have to kill you now.
Here's a secret before you die.
There is an insect deep in Southeast
Asia called the Sariporosia beetle.
Thirty thousand of
their tiny stomachs have
been dried out and then
woven into this scarf.
Their bodies conduct Harmon
far better than a human body,
thus dispersing the charge.
It's similar to an electrical ground.
I have inherited 4,000 years worth of
history and research in the art of Harmon.
Unlike Dio, I have studied the craft.
I am a master of its strengths
and flaws in all forms of combat.
Wow, that's quite impressive.
No, really? It is.
But did you think I'd completely rely on
a gimmick like Harmon all of the time?
Hmm hmm I'm also very fast what how
did you pin that grenade on my scarf
Child's play sure but I was still
able to pull one over on you wasn't
I and you Should take a look at
the grenade you just knocked away
You son of a
Oh!
Well, that was a close one.
Wha...
what the hell is he?
Smokey, I thought I told you to run.
It's too late for that now.
Please, God, I promise I won't
ever do anything bad again.
No stealing, no lying, I swear it.
Please, just save me.
He...
He's a monster.
You probably kill monsters all the time.
You know what to do, right?
Jojo?
Sure, of course I do. Great!
I knew you would! Yep.
I have a secret weapon for
situations such as this.
A secret weapon? Really?
What kind of weapon?
Why isn't it obvious?
Look at his legs, Smokey.
I basically blew them to smithereens,
and they still haven't fully healed yet.
That's our ticket then.
What do his legs have
to do with your weapon?
My legs are in great shape.
So what are you going to do then?
Run as fast as I can!
Make way! Move!
Out of the way!
This guy's insane!
Come on, follow me, straight zone.
Hey, wait up! Jojo!
I will make him pay dearly for that.
Even though I'm immortal,
it'll take some time to regenerate
after what he did to me.
This is a perfect scoop.
The papers will be falling
all over themselves.
This is my chance to break
into big-time journalism.
Pressure applied by fingertips, 235
kilograms per centimeter squared.
Leaping ability, currently
4 meters 22 centimeters.
It's behind me, isn't it?
We should be safe by now, right?
I'm afraid not, Smokey.
Do you hear that?
Do I hear what, Jojo?
The only thing I hear is the river.
No, not that. Look up!
He followed us here!
Run, Jojo, run!
I would not do that if I were you.
Run away and I'll kill her right here.
But come up and meet me,
and I will let her go.
What sort of threat is that?
I don't even know who
that woman is, you moron.
Jojo, let's run!
Whether you know this woman
or not is inconsequential.
If you flee now, I'll know
just what sort of man you are.
Rather than pursue you, I could
use this time to heal myself.
For a true coward would not seek
revenge for Speedwagon. However,
if you were to come up here
after a girl you don't even know,
then I'll see that you
are both courageous and
powerful which means you'll
present a real threat!
and continue to pursue me into the
future and I would therefore have to
eliminate you here and now I'll kill
her regardless fight me or run decide?
Go ahead and do what you think
you need to do, straightzo.
I wouldn't fight for that floozy
even if I was married to her.
Are you certain that this is the
type of game you wish to play?
It would be so easy to
tear through her neck and
open up her chest cavity
with just two fingers.
A true master of Tibetan Hamon
would never do such a thing.
Such gratuitous cruelty would be unseemly.
That...
that was a tooth!
He just ripped it right out of her mouth!
Just despicable.
This bastard has no conscience.
Consider that your last warning.
You demonic freak.
Release her strikes out!
You pay for that!
You're a vile inhuman abomination!
Your act of playing it calm belies
the fire that we see in you now.
Let's skip the pretty speeches!
Now you're mine!
Take this!
Oh no!
Fool me once, then shame on me.
But unfortunately for you, straight-so,
you'll never be able to fool me twice!
Hamon!
That's him!
Now you'll say that's impossible!
That's impossible!
I deflected your shot with
a little Hamon shot glass.
I was pretty sure you'd
go for my forehead again.
Predictability can be
quite the fatal flaw.
Give my best to Speedwagon and Howl!
Granny should be able to
sleep well tonight. Finally.
Why would you try to save me from falling?
Aren't you frightened that I still possess
enough power in me to
blow your arm clean off?
I'd like to see you try that.
I'll just pummel you into
fertilizer with my remaining arm.
I want some answers, Straightzo.
Tell me, why did you throw
Speedwagon's body into the river?
Something here just doesn't add up.
Joseph, your grandfather
Jonathan's blood flows through you.
From the outside, you appear to be opposites,
but you're both insatiably curious.
And now it is my pleasure
to warn you that your nature
has trapped you in a fate
you cannot hope to escape.
What are you talking about?
Soon you shall learn of him,
of the Pillar Man, and then you shall
finally come face to face with him.
Oh, shut up!
I'm done decoding your
rubbish straight, though.
But I threw the bodies into
the river because of him.
Don't you see, fool?
The pillar sucked deeply of the
blood from those bodies in the cave.
It was like a plant ravenously
drawing in nutrients.
It was ghastly, so I
dragged the bodies outside.
But I have no doubts now that he will
soon awaken from his 2,000-year slumber.
Not to worry.
It is fated that you
shall meet him very soon.
And when that time comes,
you shall learn his identity and
the true meaning of evolution.
Your destiny has already been written.
Is that Harmon?
So that means you must have been
creating Harmon inside your own body.
There is nothing I regret
Joseph all this time.
I planned on entering hell
while still vibrant and
filled with energy not as some
withered desiccated corpse.
I cannot tell you the ecstasy that
I have felt in being young again.
Straits are wait not yet.
I need to know more
Farewell to you Jojo
Jojo!
1938, the second world war rages,
threatening to engulf more
nations around the globe?
with each passing day.
As the German army grows, it seeks
to conquer the world with technology.
and weapons that stand at the
very cutting edge of science.
However, they also research astrology,
sorcery, alchemy, and psychic powers.
They seek to gain advantages
through every manner
imaginable in their quest
for global domination.
And it was through this
tenacity that one of their spy
networks in Mexico caught
wind of Straitzo's actions.
I'm so terribly sorry, Major von Stroheim.
My hand, it just slipped.
I don't know what happened.
Lick it.
You drew blood from me, no?
Don't make me order you to
lick my wound clean. Yes, sir.
Gently now.
I know you wouldn't want to hurt me again.
Good.
Slowly now, slowly.
Hmm.
I think the pain is going away. Now.
Be careful now!
Careful now!
Don't cut your tongue!
Pardon my interruption,
Major von Stroheim!
The old man found on the
bank of the Rio Dada!
He is now awake, Major von Stroheim!
Shall we interrogate, sir?
Are you alright, miss?
Can you tell me your name?
Allow me to escort you home, huh?
Why in the hell did you do that?
You've got some nerve calling
me a floozy, you big brute.
Just who do you think you
are anyway, huh? What?
I never said that.
No, you did.
You said that you would never
fight for a floozy like her.
Really?
Wow, I didn't mean it.
I'm really sorry about that.
It just happened, kind of.
Yeah, I'm sure it just happens
every time you talk about a woman.
Your mouth okay?
Looks like the adrenaline
from her fear just wore off.
Now it's time to find out about this
pillar man Straitzo was talking about.
I can't wait to see Mexico.
How are you feeling, Speedwagon?
There is a saying in
Europe that comes to mind.
The village in which the elderly kill
each other is not long for this world.
You have a secret, a secret that is
very dangerous and could kill us all.
I want answers now!
There appears to be a man
trapped inside this pillar.
We extracted it from the location
we got from you. Why, God?
Why do this to me?
Why couldn't you just have
let me die back there?
Why did you make me live?
It wasn't God, at least not your God.
I was the one who made you
live, but I can change that.
The Wehrmacht would like some information
from you before anything drastic happens.
You are stubborn old man.
I'm smart enough to
know that torture alone
would not give us what we want out of you.
I also know that you were penniless
when you first got to Texas.
You were nearly dead in the desert
when you found the oil fields
that would soon cause a massive
overhaul of the world's economy.
Get ready!
German medicine is the greatest
thing in the world, don't you think?
Speak and do anything!
A truth serum?
For what?
What more could you possibly want from me?
Everything!
I want to know it all!
Give me a history lesson!
Tell me about Straitzo
and about this Joe Star.
Tell us so that we can
finally awaken the Pillar Man!
No, no, you can't!
You don't know the forces
you're playing with!
He's powerful enough to destroy us all!
Make the necessary preparations
for the blood-feeding experiment.
And don't screw anything up!
Help us!
Let us do anything, please!
Hmm.
I have a proposal for you.
Go ahead and choose someone
from among yourselves.
We need blood for a very
important historic experiment.
Once you have all agreed on who will
be the one to sacrifice his life,
we will grant the rest of
you your freedom immediately.
Me!
I volunteer for it!
If I do your experiment, you promise
that you let everyone else go, right?
You are quite brave.
Courage like yours is a thing that
must be cultivated like a lush garden.
Here, we allow only the most fit to live.
Set the boy aside and
execute everyone else.
Let the experiment begin!
I'll be the roundabout.
The words will make you out and out.
I'll spend the day your way.
Call it morning driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
The music dance and sing.
They make the children really ring.
I spend the day your way.
Call it moaning, driving through the sun.
And in and out the valley.
Then all around the lake.
Milders come out of the sky.
And they stand there.
One mile over, we'll be
there and we'll see you.
Ten two summers, we'll be
there and I'll be with you.
Twenty four and five
mile over, we'll see you.
I'll be there with you.
You've no idea what he's capable of!
All I've got under my skirt
is more tequila, big boy.
Which one of you was fool
enough to disturb my slumber?
He's squeezing himself
into the ventilation, dogs!